Guide to the Edward K. Barsky Papers ALBA.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Writings
  - Barsky, Vita ? [Threats to Academic Freedom], circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Barsky, Vita ? [Co-Education and the Treatment of Women], undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kristanov, Tsvetan Angelov: Medical Services of the International Brigades in Spain (Russian), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Marti-Ibanes, Felix: "Sigerist and Spain", circa 1958 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Uribe, Vicente: "Policy of Yankee Imperialism in Spain" (translated from Mundo Obrero), 1948 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Vayo, J. Alvarez del: Articles, undated, 1949-1956 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Voros, Sandor: Unpublished Manuscript on American Hospitals & International Medical Services in Spain, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Unidentified: [Private Manufacturing of Armaments & Profiteering], undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Unidentified: [Surgery on the Front Lines], undated (Box 5, Folder 30)